Now your friends have no idea my Stand
Crush has quite a handy little helper.
Yes, my Stand Talking Mouth works wonders,
especially when it latches
onto your tongue and
forces you to say the exact
opposite of what you mean.
Narancia, that must be the reason why
you can't give us a straight answer.
It's the enemy.
Giorno!
Whatever that stand is, it's dragging
Giorno into that puddle of water?
like a ravenous shark ready for dinner!
Lil' Bomber!
That bloodthirsty beast can
jump from liquid to liquid!
and somehow take Giorno with him?
no matter the amount of liquid there is!
Mmm, that bite was juicy.
Now to end it.
If we can take Giovanna and his
life-giving stand out of play,
killing the rest of these perdenti will
be as easy as falling off a swirling log.
So true.
Everything's going swimmingly.
However, we shouldn't dawdle.
Let's choke the life form from
the boy and be done with it.
Our intel says Narancia's stand is
a bonafide carbon dioxide detector.
So you may have well
knocked Giorno unconscious,
but given that he's still breathing, your
stand is still on Lil' Bomber's radar.
Even your puddle jumping
won't escape his notice.
The last thing we want is that puny plane
finding us and giving them the upper hand.
They'd be on us in seconds.
Yes, I agree, Tiziano.
Giorno will breathe no more.
I'll make sure of it
Thank you.
Yeah, I got you!
Oh, shit!
That thing is gonna take
Giorno away and kill him!
Damn this bastardo.
Instead of one stand to deal with, there
have been a pair of stands all along.
God!
Ah!
Oh, damn it!
I can't hit this guy for shit!
And the more I miss my mark, the more
chances I'm giving him to escape!
I've got to start anticipating his
moves! Where is he? Where'd he go?
There!
He can teleport till
he's blue in the face!
As long as I stay one step
ahead of him, I can win!
The boy's using his radar again.
As I said, he seeks to find and kill us.
We have to halt Giorno's
breathing immediately.
Simmer down.
It's under control, Teets.
But you know, attacking Giorno while
teleporting isn't exactly a walk in the park!
Now we're in sync! Fire!
I hit his neck!
Giorno!
I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to...
What the hell?!
His breathing!
I'm not picking up his breathing!
Why isn't the radar detecting anything?
Son of a bitch!
He got away from me!
Well, he's a goner now.
Crush has taken him for
a ride in the sewer.
I'll have it swim to the canal and
dump off the dead weight there.
Hang on a sec, Squalo.
What the hell was that?
Huh?
I was just saying that I'd dump his body.
Not that.
I mean Narancia.
It was far away, but I know what I heard.
It was Narancia's voice
shouting something.
He was screaming about
it getting away from him.
Huh?
Right now, Talking Mouse should
still be affixed to his tongue.
There's no way the kid should
still be able to speak the truth.
How in the hell did he choke that out?
He even said the radar
wasn't picking anything up.
Move, Squalo!
You have to get away from there now!
What are you talking about?
I guarantee you Giorno's
never gonna breathe again.
There's no way anyone
can snip out Crush now.
I think it might be overreacting.
No, he said it got away on purpose.
He did it in order to
make you drop your guard.
Can't you see he was trying to get
you to stall your next teleportation?
For the life of me, I
don't know how he did it,
but the bastards found a
way to track your movements.
That's it.
Giorno moved into my
line of fire on purpose.
He used the gun smoke to
give me a trail one that'll
lead me right back to the
enemy It's crystal clear.
I can see that stinking guppy a mile away.
All right
How do you like that hate to ruin your
plans But you're no still hasn't been the
big one if we can revive him in the next
few minutes We might be able to save him!
We're in trouble, Squalo!
He's already nailed you
twice with that gun,
so all he has to do is
follow the smoke back to us!
Yes!
I drove the scumbag out of the sewer!
Well, I'm stuck, Bucciarati.
This is about as far back
as I can go with this guy.
Based on the replay, our attacker was
in the cup on this table at one point.
But whatever it was, it left in a hurry.
Unfortunately,
Moody Jazz can't transform beyond
this time, and it can't move either.
What are you trying to say, Abakyo?
I'm not sure.
It's almost like this thing can teleport.
This bastard's got me stumped.
I just can't replay
enough to see the user.
It's like the videotape
has been severed somehow.
Damn it!
I didn't think Narancia was this clever!
He's not, it was Giorno!
We're in this mess because he decided to
let himself get mauled by Lil' Bomber.
We played into his hands
and didn't even know it.
Come on!
I can't get rid of the residue!
It must be because he was
hit with stand bullets.
Even the water can't
get this grunt off me!
I've got to find somewhere to hide.
Somewhere his detectors
won't be able to find me.
Great, we're playing this game again.
All right, think!
This ugly-looking shark thing may have
crazy speed for a long-range stand,
but from what I've seen, it can't get
very far with one of its teleports.
It can only move two to
three meters per jump!
Shit!
Oh, man!
He's predicting my moves and
his aim is getting more precise!
He's slowing down!
It must be his injuries!
Squalo, no!
Yeah, I got him!
Just one more direct hit
and then it's bye-bye fishy.
Now go to hell, you bottom feeder!
What's that smell?
There's a gas leak!
This is all going according
to plan, Narancia.
Thanks to your ace shooting,
the hot water spilt out of the
pot and put out the flames.
How's a little bomber gonna shoot
me in this gaseous death trap?
My quick thinking has rendered
your tracking skills a moot point.
But by all means, fire
away and ignite the gas.
Doing so might not kill you,
but everything around you
will be set ablaze and
the resulting carbon dioxide
will nullify your radar.
What's wrong, Narancia?
You seem to be hesitating.
Shoot already!
Secure our victory!
So what if I can't shoot your ass to hell?
There are plenty of ways
to fillet a homicidal fish!
I did it!
I finished him off!
Bucciarati, Mista, the enemy is here!
Abacchio, he has the ability to
transport himself from liquid to liquid!
Good, he's breathing again.
Hang on, I just told the truth.
I've regained control over what I say.
It's been done.
I've gone ahead and released Talking
Mouth from Narancia just as you planned.
This was a brilliant strategy.
You've sustained several injuries,
but I'm sure the boss will be pleased.
What's all the racket, Narancia?
You said you found the enemy?
But Talking Mouth's
release is only temporary.
Why is Jean...
Is that the enemy's stand?
Oh, no!
Wait, don't!
This is how you secure
victory, my dear Squalo.
It's time to complete our mission.
Here we go, six bullets!
Fire away, mister!
What the hell just happened?
Shit!
My radar's going crazy!
He's gonna strike and I can't track him!
That bastard's gonna kill Giorno all
because I can't tell the freaking truth!
Narancia, you have to look for it.
Giorno, you're awake!
The user.
Forget the stand and go
after the stand's user.
Giorno, look out!
Hey, Narancia!
You idiots,
why in the hell would
you give me the all-clear
to shoot when this place
is a ticking time bomb?
Watch out! There it is!
The enemy's above you!
No!
He's below you, damn it!
What the?
This is so messed up.
I'm screwed.
The lies just keep coming.
I've got to stop talking.
He's gone.
No doubt he'll kill Giorno first.
Then he'll start wiping
out the rest of us.
The user.
Forget the stand and go after.
The stand's user.
Giorno.
Giorno told me to go after the user.
That's right, the user's injured.
Which means he's probably breathing
pretty heavily at the moment.
Of course, that's it.
He wants me to use my
radar to find the bastard.
I've gotta do this.
And it's gotta be on my own.
Now, where is he?
I know the guy's a long-range stand user
But he has to be around here somewhere
I'm out of time!
This fool dies now!
The plan's going off without a hitch.
With Giorno out of the picture, they
won't be able to play doctor anymore.
Now drive the nail in Giorno's coffin.
His time's come.
It'd be my pleasure.
I'm not quite at my best.
But I still have enough juice
left to knock him to kingdom come.
Hey, look. It's Narancia.
What's he doing out here?
Where exactly is Crush right now?
It's over there.
It went out of the sewer, over by the
restaurant, and is heading toward the canal.
He shouldn't be able to track it anymore.
Surely he couldn't be trying
to hunt me down, could he?
My breathing should be untraceable.
It's madness!
Calm yourself, Squalo.
No need to fear.
All this is just his feeble
attempt at victory. Tell me,
how many pedestrians do you think are
walking around this hundred meter radius?
Fifty? A hundred?
He can't tell you from anyone
else walking around down there.
But I'm injured.
What if he picks up on the
unnatural breathing and
decides to follow that trail
all the way back to me?
You have to collect yourself.
Look at the bottom of the stairs.
Several people down there are
breathing a lot harder than you,
so all you need to do is allow
your breathing to settle.
If we walk into that piazza like nothing
is wrong, everything will work out.
Fact of the matter is,
we've won this fight.
Yeah, you're right.
We've got this in the bag now.
There's no way Flyboy can find us.
I've got you, Stronto!
You can't hide from me!
What?
Impossible!
Damn it!
I have to recall Crush!
You have to relax, Squalo.
Just think for a minute!
Everything he's saying is the
exact opposite of what he intends.
He said he found you, which means
he has no clue where we are.
Don't forget he's still under my power.
If that's really true, why would
he bother saying anything at all?
Isn't it obvious he's trying to get you
riled up and throw your
breathing off kilter?
Just calm down, otherwise you'll
be doing exactly what he wants.
Believe me when I say that whiny
brat could never single you out.
This is his last-ditch
effort to rattle you.
Think calmly and get your
breathing under control.
There!
I found you! You're dead!
Come here, asshat!
You're finally about to get
everything that's coming to you!
Did you hear that?
It's going to be okay.
Trust me, he hasn't found us.
It doesn't matter what he says.
Every word he utters is a big lie.
You know my power still has hold over him.
As long as Talking Mouth is
gripping his tongue, we're fine.
Deeds, about that.
What?
How the hell did he?
I can't believe it.
He sliced off his tongue
and he used his own knife.
That...
that shouldn't be possible.
How's this lunatic even
conscious, let alone speaking?
It's crazy!
Who is this freak show?
I found you!
Now die!
What?
He has another tongue?
He used that ladybug.
But how?
It must have been that Giorno brat!
He used his stamp to transform it!
The boss was totally right!
That guy's bad news!
Giorno had to have made
Naranja a replacement
tongue back when they
were both in the kitchen!
He's coming!
We're dead for sure!
He was monitoring my
breathing the whole time!
No, he's just trying to trick us!
If the bastard had actually detected you,
he would have made his
move a long time ago!
There are so many people here, all
with different types of breathing.
Some are shallow while others are deeper.
Singling someone out should be impossible,
but I've been waiting patiently.
for a very special moment.
The moment when you lost your
cool and revealed yourself to me.
And now that you've seen
my hacked-off tongue,
your agitated breathing is a
shining beacon leading right to you!
Bet you never thought
you'd see this stand?
hanging like a hunk of meat, which is
why you're descending into a panic!
It was well worth the wait!
And here I was just about to
give up on looking for ya!
Hey! You there!
Breathing kinda heavy?
What you trying to play dumb?
Don't pretend like you don't hear
me a long-haired punk rock reject.
This is insane He
mutilated his own body so
he could find our location
that guy's a maniac.
Well now what a surprise I take
it the guy next to you is the
user of that shark stand and I
gotta say He's looking pretty pale.
I want to get that checked out
Recall crush and do it fast.
I'm already on it.
He's swimming through the sewer as we
speak and making a beeline for that Well,
the problem is, there's
no water in the square.
It can't attack unless it has
a body of liquid to leap from.
You are the one!
The bastard who tried to
sneak away with Giorno!
No, Tiziano!
This should be more than
enough for you to use.
Give him hell, Squalo.
Things may not have gone as
planned, but one thing remains true.
Victories within our grasp.
Nobody can reverse our conquest now.
To hell with the boss!
He can shove his orders
up his reclusive ass!
I'm not gonna murder you because it's
my duty as one of the boss's guards.
This is for you Tiziano, I'll send this
piece of shit to hell in your name!
Once I'm done his friends will die too.
I'll eviscerate them for what they
did Suffering will be their penance.
Finish him crush rip his
throat out tear it to shreds!
Give me a break!
What you think this would work!
You really thought something
like this would take me down?
I'm telling you right now.
We are getting out of here.
We're leaving this place behind with
all of our lives intact Nice knowing
Volare via!
You're nothing but a traitor!
The only thing waiting for you beyond this
place is death and despair
at the boss's hand!
What the hell keeps these
treasonous dogs going?
Surely they still don't
have hope, even now!
What is it with them?
Giorno!
What a relief!
He's finally breathing again!
Giorno!
Wake up! Giorno! Giorno!
Hey, Narancia.
I know a Bakio would
never want to admit this,
but it was your decision-making that
pulled us through this whole mess.
I don't know where we'd
even be without you.
You've become our leader!
There might actually be some hope
for us yet, with you by our side.
Come on, Giorno.
Everyone's waiting.
How long ago did that attack begin
four or five minutes let's get moving
it's safe to say Venice is free of
Hitman from the Family we're in the clear
let's head to the airport now we're
taking to the skies that'll get us to our
next destination we're headed for the
isle of sardinia If we're to succeed,
it's imperative that we
uncover the boss's past.
Our lives depend on it.
Join us Come on You'll see us alive
We are the power Cause there's a future
Cause we are the fighters Just fighting
for the right We are the fighters
We are the fighters We are the fighters
Thank you.
You